Finding Aid for the Louis Jolyon West Papers LSC.0590
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 7. Research Files., 1890-1996.
  - 7.1 Research A to Z., 1890-1996.
    - Terrorism--Research proposal by Jeanne N. Knutson "The Psychodynamics of Political Terrorism"., 1979. (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Terrorism--"Toward a United States Policy of Terrorism" draft paper by Jeanne N. Knutson., 1981. (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Terrorism--"The Dynamics of the Hostage Taker: Some Major Variants," by Jeanne N. Knutson., 1979. (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Terrorism--Jeanne N. Knutson papers., 1979-1981. (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Terrorism--Correspondence, budgets, event flyer, and notes regarding Jeanne N. Knutson research., 1980-1982, 1987. (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Terrorism--Compensation for victims., 1985-1986. (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Terrorism--Articles by authors with last names "A" through "F"., 1976, 1978-1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1990. (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Terrorism--Articles by authors with last names "G" through "P"., 1977-1978, 1980-1981, 1983-1987. (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Terrorism--Articles by authors with last names "Q" through "Z"., 1977, 1979-1980, 1983, 1985, 1987, 1991. (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Terrorism--Clippings., 1974, 1976, 1979-1981, 1983, 1986-1987, 1990, 1993. (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, Alexander., 1974-1975, 1977, 1981. (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Torture--International Conference for the Abolition of Torture and the Treatment of Victims (The Johnson Foundation Wingspread Conference) materials and LJW notes (1 of 2)., 1979, 1983. (Box 176, Folder 6)
      See also "Violence"
    - Torture--International Conference for the Abolition of Torture and the Treatment of Victims (The Johnson Foundation Wingspread Conference) materials and LJW notes (2 of 2)., 1957, 1960, 1962, 1966, 1982-1983. (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Torture--International Conference for the Abolition of Torture and the Treatment of Victims (The Johnson Foundation Wingspread Conference) transcripts (1 of 2)., 1983. (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Torture--International Conference for the Abolition of Torture and the Treatment of Victims (The Johnson Foundation Wingspread Conference) transcripts (2 of 2)., 1983. (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Torture--International Rehabilitation and Research Centre for Torture Victims, correspondence and articles (1 of 2)., 1982-1986. (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Torture--International Rehabilitation and Research Centre for Torture Victims, correspondence and articles (2 of 2)., ca. 1985. (Box 177, Folder 5)
      Includes articles for anthology.
    - Torture--Bibliography., 1986. (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Torture--"On Torture" manuscript by group at International Rehabilitation and Research Center for Torture Victims; includes LJW correspondence., 1985. (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Torture--Torture victims., 1977, 1980-1983, 1987. (Box 178, Folder 3)
      Includes materials labeled "Source material for slides on torture" and materials from University of Chicago "Victims of Torture: Meeting the Needs" conference.
    - Torture--Center for Victims of Torture., 1979, 1989, 1992-1993. (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Torture--Amnesty International reports (1 of 2)., 1979-1980, 1983-1984, 1990. (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Torture--Amnesty International miscellaneous materials, correspondence, and clippings (2 of 2)., 1984, 1986, 1989-1992. (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Torture--American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS)., 1985-1988. (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Torture--Methods and war., 1957, 1960, 1965, 1970, 1983, 1986. (Box 178, Folder 8)
      Includes LJW, "Psychopathology Produced by Sleep Deprivation."
    - Torture--Physicians for Human Rights., 1989, 1991. (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Torture--Science and human rights., 1949, 1981-1984. (Box 179, Folder 2)
      Includes materials from the Antislavery Society for the Protection of Human Rights.
    - Torture--Solitary confinement and sensory isolation., 1969, 1972, 1974-1976, 1981, 1983-1984, 1988-1991, 1993. (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Torture--Iraq., 1981. (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Torture--Articles by authors with last names "A" through "K"., 1971-1974, 1978-1986, 1988-1989, 1994. (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Torture--Articles by authors with last names "L" through "Z" (1 of 2)., 1966, 1969, 1973, 1976, 1980-1981, 1983-1987, 1993. (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Torture--Articles by authors with last names "L" through "Z" (2 of 2)., 1966, 1969, 1973, 1976, 1980-1981, 1983-1987, 1993. (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Tourette's Syndrome., 1973, 1975-1976, 1978. (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Transient Global Amnesia., 1991. (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Trauma--Center for Traumatic Stress Disorders proposals (1 of 4)., ca. 1984-1986. (Box 180, Folder 3)
      See also "Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder," "Torture"
    - Trauma--Center for Traumatic Stress Disorders proposal to the Robert Ellis Simon Foundation (2 of 4)., 1985-1986. (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Trauma--Center for Traumatic Stress Disorders proposal correspondence and notes (3 of 4)., 1984-1986. (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Trauma--Center for Traumatic Stress Disorders references (4 of 4)., ca. 1982-1985. (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Tremor., 1991. (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Tsuang, Ming T.., 1974-1981. (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Twain, Mark., 1974. (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - UFOs., 1991-1992. (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - University of Oklahoma Medical Center Behavioral Sciences program grant application., 1968. (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Vietnam--"Violations of Human Rights in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam: April 30, 1975-April 30, 1983," by Ginetta Sagan and Stephen Denny. (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Violence--LJW "Epidemiology of Violence" talk (1 of 2)., 1982. (Box 181, Folder 6)
      Includes "Epidemiology of Violence" abstract, perhaps also by LJW.
    - Violence--"Epidemiology of Violence" talk, notes, statistics, and articles (2 of 2)., 1970, 1984-1988. (Box 181, Folder 7)
      Includes LJW article "Biosocial Adaptation and Correlates of Aculturation in the Tarahumara Ecosystem" and LJW talk "Violence: A Psychiatric Perspective."
    - Violence--Bibliography and "The Epidemiology of Violence" literature review., 1987, ca. 1989, 1991. (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Violence--LJW "Suicide and Violence Project" statistics (1 of 4)., 1974-1978, 1981, 1983. (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Violence--LJW "Suicide and Violence Project" notes and articles (2 of 4)., ca. 1971, 1977, 1980, 1986-1987. (Box 181, Folder 10)
      Includes notes for LJW lecture.
    - Violence--LJW "Suicide and Violence Project" clippings (3 of 4)., 1974, 1980-1981. (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Violence--LJW "Suicide and Violence Project" New Zealand, Australia, UK, Canada, US statistics, articles, and notes (4 of 4)., ca. 1979, 1983. (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Violence--Correspondence and meeting agendas., 1981, 1985, 1989, 1992. (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Violence--Correspondence, statistics, notes, and articles concerning violence in Canada, Australia, New Zealand, the United Kingdom., 1984, 1987, 1989-1992. (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Violence--Homelessness (1 of 4)., 1988-1989. (Box 182, Folder 4)
      Concerns veterans and homelessness, LJW correspondence with Veterans Administration.
    - Violence--Homelessness (2 of 4)., 1988. (Box 182, Folder 5)
      Includes studies from Department of Housing and Urban Development, LJW correspondence with the Interagency Council on the Homeless.
    - Violence--Homelessness (3 of 4)., 1984. (Box 182, Folder 6)
      Includes report from the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development.
    - Violence--Homelessness (4 of 4)., 1988. (Box 183, Folder 1)
      Includes reports from the City of New York Human Resources Administration.
    - Violence--Statistical data, articles, and 1985 slide material (1 of 12)., 1960-1961, 1965, 1970, 1980, 1984. (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Violence--Statistics and data up to 1985 (2 of 12)., ca. 1985. (Box 183, Folder 3)
      Data and charts probably for LJW slides.
    - Violence--Statistics and 1991 slides (3 of 12)., ca. 1990-1991. (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Violence--Statistics and slides concerning violence from 1960 to 1989 (4 of 12)., ca. 1989, 1991-1992. (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Violence--Statistics and slides (5 of 12)., ca. 1989-1990. (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Violence--Statistics and slides (6 of 12)., ca. 1986, 1989. (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Violence--Statistics, slides, notes, and articles (7 of 12)., ca. 1989, 1991. (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Violence--Collective violence statistics, articles, and clippings (8 of 12)., 1985, ca. 1988-1990. (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Violence--Statistics and slides from LJW folder labeled "Graphs and Charts-- Archive" (9 of 12)., ca. 1988, 1992. (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Violence--School violence statistics, slides, and articles (10 of 12)., ca. 1989-1991. (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Violence--Suicide statistics (11 of 12)., ca. 1991. (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Violence--1991-1992 Statistics (12 of 12)., ca. 1992. (Box 184, Folder 3)
      Includes LJW itinerary for trip to Stanford, 1992, 11-12 March.
    - Violence--New Zealand violence statistics., 1980-1981, 1985-1986. (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Violence--Australia violence statistics., 1961, 1975-1978, 1982, 1984, 1986. (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Violence--Materials concerning James W. Prescott research., 1973, 1975-1977, 1979, 1981-1982. (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Violence--Fred Loya et al research proposal "A Typological Description of Violent Death: An Ecological Approach"., 1978. (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Violence--LJW winter 1993 course on Mental Health Services in UCLA School of Public Health., 1992-1993. (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Violence--LJW notes., 1993 [?]. (Box 184, Folder 9)
      Notes are perhaps for winter 1993 course on Mental Health Services in UCLA School of Public Health.
    - Violence--LJW fall 1991 UCLA School of Medicine InterActive Teaching course on Violence., 1989-1991. (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Violence--International Society for Research on Aggression., 1984, 1986. (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Violence--Center for Disease Control., 1983-1984, 1988-1989. (Box 185, Folder 3)
      Includes materials concerning the Year 2000 National Health Objectives to Reduce Violent and Abusive Behavior.
    - Violence--Society for the Prevention of Violence., 1986, 1989, 1991. (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Violence--California Commission on Crime Control and Violence Prevention., 1981-1982. (Box 185, Folder 5)
      Includes LJW slide material and LJW testimony as part of California Commission on Crime Control and Violence Prevention hearing in Oakland.
    - Violence--Materials from the International Association for the Study of Medical Psychology, the Latham Foundation, and the Begun Institute., 1983, 1988. (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Violence--National Coalition on Television Violence., 1993-1986. (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Violence--Violence and the Media., 1978, 1982-1985, 1990. (Box 185, Folder 8)
      Includes materials for 1984-1985 Medicine and Society Forum. May also include materials for LJW course at UCLA.
    - Violence--News clippings (1 of 2)., 1973-1978, 1981, 1984-1987, 1991, 1993-1994. (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Violence--News clippings (2 of 2)., 1978, 1980-1981, 1983-1985, 1989-1994. (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Violence--Victims., 1984, 1987-1990. (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Violence--Blaming the victim., 1971-1972, 1976, 1979, 1982-1984, 1987. (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Violence--Freeway shootings in Los Angeles and mass media., 1981-1982, 1897. (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Violence--Television violence., 1973-1976. (Box 186, Folder 6)
      Includes LJW talk "Research on Violence, Problems and Possibilities."
    - Violence--Materials related to the National Conference of Christians and Jews "Serving Survivors" conference., 1984-1985, 1988. (Box 186, Folder 7)
      `
    - Violence--War., 1991-1992. (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Violence--Aggression., 1968, 1971. (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Violence--Homicide in Los Angeles, 1970-1979., 1984, 1986. (Box 187, Folder 3)
      Includes "The Epidemiology of Homicide in Los Angeles, 1970-1979," by Fred Loya, Nancy H. Allen, Luis Vargas.
    - Violence--Gangs., 1992-1993. (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Violence--Guns., 1985-1992. (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Violence--Murder-Suicide., 1970, 1976, 1978, 1980, 1982-1983, 1985. (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Violence--Violence in emergency rooms (1 of 2)., 1969, 1982-1983, 1986, 1988-1992. (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Violence--Violence in emergency rooms (2 of 2)., 1984, 1991-1992. (Box 187, Folder 8)
      Includes materials probably for LJW slide presentation.
    - Violence--Violence in the workplace., ca. 1991. (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Violence--Violence in schools., 1978-1979, 1984-1990. (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Violence--Cannibalism., 1992. (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - Violence--Serial killers., 1985, 1988-1989, 1991-1992, 1994. (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Violence--Domestic violence., 1975, 1984, 1986-1987, 1989-1990, 1992-1994. (Box 188, Folder 2)
      Includes slide material for LJW presentation.
    - Violence--Psychiatry and the law: assessing dangerousness., 1983-1985, 1987-1990. (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Violence--Articles by authors with last names "A" through "H"., 1958, 1963, 1974-1977, 1979-1986, 1988-1989. (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Violence--Articles by authors with last names "J" through "P" (1 of 2)., 1967, 1974, 1978, 1983-1984, 1988-1989. (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Violence--Articles by authors with last names "J" through "P" (2 of 2)., 1973, 1976, 1983-1986,1988, 1993. (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Violence--Articles by authors with last names "R" through "Z" (1 of 2)., 1968, 1975, 1977-1978, 1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1988, 1990. (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Violence--Articles by authors with last names "R" through "Z" (2 of 2)., 1981, 1984, 1987, 1989- 1992. (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Violence--Collective violence articles by authors with last names "A" through "K" (1 of 2)., 1967, 1974, 1976, 1978-1979, 1984, 1986. (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Violence--Collective violence articles by authors with last names "A" through "K" (2 of 2)., 1972-1974, 1976-1977, 1982, 1986-1987, 1990-1992. (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Violence--Collective violence articles by authors with last names "L" through "Z" (1 of 2)., 1972-1974, 1976, 1978-1979, 1983-1984, 1988. (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Violence--Collective violence articles by authors with last names "L" through "Z" (2 of 2)., 1967, 1972-1974, 1976, 1978-1979, ca. 1987. (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Violence--Materials from the American Psychiatric Association, the Clarke Institute of Psychiatry, the UCLA Brain Research Institute, and the Violence and Victims journal., 1974, 1993. (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Violence--Roland D. Maiuro research., 1987, 1989. (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Violence--Murray A. Straus research and correspondence with LJW., 1973, 1977-1979. (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Violence--Robert Plutchik research., ca. 1981. (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Violence--Robert S. Pynoos research and correspondence with LJW., ca. 1982. (Box 190, Folder 6)
      See also "Pynoos, Robert. S"
    - Violence--LJW lecture and article reprints., 1965, 1967. (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Warfare--Unclassified paper "Communist Bacteriological Warfare Propaganda"., 1968. (Box 190, Folder 8)
      Handwritten text on paper probably states: CPI Special Paper No. 4, Coordinator of Psychological Intelligence, Dept. of State.
    - Westinghouse project draft and correspondence., 1963. (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Whitman, Charles J.., 1966-1967. (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - XYY Syndrome., 1965-1968. (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - Rolodex cards of research subjects "A" to "B"., ca. 1954-1994 [?]. (Box 190, Folder 12)
      Includes section "Alcoholism"
    - Rolodex cards of research subjects "C" to "Dreams"., ca. 1954-1994 [?]. (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Rolodex cards of research subjects "Drugs" to "He-"., ca. 1954-1994 [?]. (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Rolodex cards of research subjects "Hippies" to "O"., ca. 1954-1994 [?]. (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Rolodex cards of research subjects "P"., ca. 1954-1994 [?]. (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Rolodex cards of research subjects "R" to "Z"., ca. 1954-1994 [?]. (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Index cards: "Brainwashing" and "Hallucination" bibliographies., ca. 1979. (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Index cards: "Alcoholism" bibliographies., ca. 1979. (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Index cards: "Meditation" bibliographies., ca. 1979. (Box 192, Folder 4)
      Includes cards labeled "final bibliography."
    - Index cards: "References not to be used in bibliography"., ca. 1979. (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Index cards: Miscellaneous bibliography materials., ca. 1979. (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Hallucinations (1 of 2) (oversized materials)., 1962-1963, 1965-1967. (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Hallucinations (2 of 2) (oversized materials)., 1966-1967. (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Oklahoma City teen rape case., 1965. (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Diagram of Center structure., undated. (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Drugs and drug abuse--Jones case, oversized documents., 1976. (Box 193, Folder 5)
      Oversized--with items in 8.5 x 14" document box.
    - Fan Mail Project--oversized artwork and letters., ca. 1961. (Box 193, Folder 6)
      Folder contains letters and artwork by a fan for Charlton Heston. Oversized--with items in 8.5 x 14" document box.
    - Holocaust--oversized material., 1982. (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Law and psychiatry--oversized materials., 1964, 1969, ca. 1982. (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Military prisoners of war (P.O.W.s)--Research design (oversized materials)., ca. 1954. (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Nixon, Richard (oversized materials)., 1974. (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Pain--Patient-Controlled Analgesia (oversized materials)., 1979-1980, 1982-1983, 1986-1987, 1990-1991. (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Audio Recording "SLA #1"., 1974 February 12. (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Audio Recording "SLA #2"., 1974 February 16. (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Audio Recording "SLA #3"., 1974 February 20. (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Audio Recording "SLA #4"., 1974 March 9. (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Audio Recording "SLA #5"., 1974 April 3. (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Audio Recording "SLA #6"., 1974 April 24. (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Hearst, Patricia Campbell--Audio Recording "SLA #7"., 1974 June 7. (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Audio recording--Suicide Prevention Week, 1974 radio spots with Charlton Heston (American Association of Suicidology). (Box 194, Folder 9)
      See also "Suicide--National Institute of Mental Health National Suicide Prevention Week (1974 May 19-25) materials"
    - Slides--LJW charts, figures on sleep., ca. 1959-1969. (Box 194, Folder 22)
      Some slides damaged. See also "Sleep--LJW charts, figures."
    - Film--"Suicide Prevention Week, 1974" TV spot with Charlton Heston (National Institute of Mental Health). (Box 194, Folder 23)
      See also"Suicide--National Institute of Mental Health National Suicide Prevention Week (1974 May 19-25) materials"
    - Parapsychology--news clippings and interview (oversized folder)., 1970, 1972-1973, 1977-1979. (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Police--Rodney King and police violence news clippings (1 of 2) (oversized materials)., 1991-1992. (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Police--Rodney King and police violence news clippings (2 of 2) (oversized materials)., 1983-1984, 1987, 1991-1992. (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Psychopharmacology--unpublished work by LJW (oversized materials)., 1947, 1956-1957. (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Religion--Materials concerning LJW's "Religion and Psychiatry" chapter in Religion in Philosophical and Cultural Perspective (oversized materials)., 1962-1964. (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Right to die--News clippings (oversized materials)., 1970, 1987, 1989-1994, 1996. (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Seth (Egyptian god)., 1967. (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Tarahumara--Clippings (oversize materials)., 1968-1970, 1972, 1979-1980, 1994. (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Medical Television Network posters: Winter Series 1966, March 1966 Programs (oversize materials)., 1966 winter, 1966 March. (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - Psychotherapy--Robot therapist (oversize materials)., 1961-1962. (Box 249, Folder 3)
      Correspondence and diagram from John A. Foster. Additional folded copy of poster in "Psychotherapy--Robot therapist."
  - 7.2 Cults., 1942-1996.
    - Audio recording--LJW, "Cult Phenomenon: Overview"., undated. (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Audio recording--LJW at UCLA Neuropsychiatric Institute., 1989 May 25. (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - VHS cassette: America's Black Forum, Show #112 (length:30:00)., 1986 February 11. (Box 50, Folder 11)
      Julian Bond, host; with Heber Jensch, Joseph Paige, Rabbi David S. Ben-Ami, Rev. Jim Nichols (First Church of God)
    - Audio recording--Sandi Gallant on "Satanic Cults"., 1986 April 28. (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Audio recording--Rosedale, "Lawyer's Perspective of Cults" (1 of 6)., undated. (Box 194, Folder 11)
      See also "Notes from box with cult-related audio recordings"
    - Audio recording--Singer, "Mental Health Perspective of Cults" (2 of 6)., undated. (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Audio recording--Robbins, "Religious Implications of Cults" (3 of 6)., undated. (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Audio recording--Delgado, "Constitutional Perspective of Cults" (4 of 6)., undated. (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - Audio recording--Gary Scharff, "Insider's View of Cults" (5 of 6)., undated. (Box 194, Folder 15)
    - Audio recording--Winslade [?], "Reflections on Conference" (6 of 6)., undated. (Box 194, Folder 16)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program: Gary Scharff and Hilly Zeitlan on "Exit Counseling" (1 of 2)., 1981 October 27. (Box 194, Folder 17)
      Includes note: "Transcribed by SBC, 11-4-81 (see file copy)."
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program: Gary Scharff and Hilly Zeitlan on "Exit Counseling" (2 of 2)., 1981 October 27. (Box 194, Folder 18)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program: Hardat Sukhdeo, Dale Parks, and Odell Rhodes on "Jonestown: How Did It Happen?" (1 of 3)., 1981 October 13. (Box 194, Folder 19)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program: Hardat Sukhdeo, Dale Parks, and Odell Rhodes on "Jonestown: How Did It Happen?" (2 of 3)., 1981 October 13. (Box 194, Folder 20)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program: Hardat Sukhdeo, Dale Parks, and Odell Rhodes on "Jonestown: How Did It Happen?" (3 of 3)., 1981 October 13. (Box 194, Folder 21)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program on Cult-Related Mental Health Issues: Bijan Etemad and Meyer Lightman on "Treatment" (1 of 2)., 1981 October 6. (Box 194, Folder 24)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program on Cult-Related Mental Health Issues: Bijan Etemad and Meyer Lightman on "Treatment" (2 of 2)., 1981 October 6. (Box 194, Folder 25)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program on Cult-Related Mental Health Issues: Paul Morantz on "Legal Issues" (1 of 2)., 1981 November 17. (Box 194, Folder 26)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program on Cult-Related Mental Health Issues: Paul Morantz on "Legal Issues" (2 of 2)., 1981 November 17. (Box 194, Folder 27)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program on Cult-Related Mental Health Issues: Father Kent Burtner and Rabbi A. James Rudin on "The Religious Search" (1 of 2)., 1981 November 23. (Box 194, Folder 28)
    - Audio recording--In-Service Training Program on Cult-Related Mental Health Issues: Father Kent Burtner and Rabbi A. James Rudin on "The Religious Search" (2 of 2)., 1981 November 23. (Box 194, Folder 29)